Now the others come.
- Hello.
- It's been a bit noisy.
- I know.
Welcome to the parking lot.
Or, the small lawn next to the parking lot.
- in Stenstorp.
- I know, I know.
Listen, can't you be the same?
- please?
- Please please?
- Can't we bury the battle ax?
- (Harry) okay.
(Alma) okay.
- (Axel) Hug!
- (Alma) hugs!
Now we are going here, at the Dalénium Science Center.
(Axel) please!
Oh, Harry holds up the door.
Brilliant.
(Axel) Hi, Hi!
The boat is just 50 meters from our tents.
This will be exciting.
"Going a boat" was a bit ... exaggerated.
We are actually going out and quiet.
- On this river.
- Yes.
- called Tidan, and goes through Tidaholm.
Good!
Professional, Harry.
Here comes a year!
- "Don't Kill Me."
(Don't kill me.) - No, I'm not going to kill you.
- No, we are wrong.
- Nämen, now you back.
Wait, Harry.
Stop.
Harry, stop!
Shouldn't I be resting instead?
- (Axel) Oh, what good with food.
- (Joanna) Sooo tasty.
Oh my God, what a cheese pizza!
And gluten -free, to Alma's great happiness.
(Shoulder) SuperMight.
We have just done ourselves at this center behind it.
There are type kitchens, laundry rooms, toilets, showers, and stuff.
And now let's go back to our tent and sleep.
- (Joanna) How are we going to sleep, then?
- We will sleep girl tents and tents.
- (Axel, Hest) huh?!
- Yes.
- What was that voice?!
- (shoulder, crash) "huh?!"
(Light voice) "I'm a girl."
(Regular voice) No, but I like to sleep with Harry!